zeeptravel.com 2011-05-19

# Privacy Policy

| WAKANOW’S PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT |   
---|---|---  

  * Wakanow is strongly committed to the protection of your privacy online and accordingly, we take protective measures to protect the personal information provided to us by you. We also take further measures to comply with the relevant statement regarding what we can do with personal information we obtain from you.
  * We are notified under the Data Protection Act 1998 and intend to comply with all our obligations under that Act. You consent to our processing of your information.
  * This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not, create any contractual or other legal rights or obligations on either your or our part.
  * In order to assist us, you may provide us with information from time to time which we may require or use for the purposes of providing you with any required services, information or requested activity including contacting you and providing notification to you in relation to such services or related activity.
  * Wakanow may collect and use the following kinds of personal information provided by you for the purposes of registering with us, information about transactions carried out over the website, information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to Wakanow’s services and any other information that you send to Wakanow Travel network Limited.
  * Wakanow may use your personal information to send to you services and products that you purchase, supply to you services that you purchase, send you statements and invoices, collect payments from you and send you marketing communications.
  * Where Wakanow discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.
  * In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Wakanow may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
  * We may provide the data collected from you to members of our group companies or other third party including our agents and contractors in connection with the service. We will inform you prior to disclosing your information to any third party. If you can be identified from the information that is disclosed, then we will not disclose such information without prior notification to you and we will obtain your permission to do so. **You may inform us at any time not to pass on or share your personal information with any third parties.**
  * The registration information you provide may be required to use the service or Site. We will store this information and data and use it to contact you, provide you with further details of the services and otherwise for the normal use, provision of services and improvement of the Site, unless you ask us not to do so.
  * The information may be disclosed to third parties to enable you to gain access to any restricted part of the Site, enable you to receive information, which you have requested to be sent to you by post or for you to receive specified services.
  * Information that Wakanow collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Wakanow operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
  * We may use cookies to store and track information about you. This will assist us in measuring the effectiveness of banner advertising and provide more accurate analysis of site activity. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer.
  * We are taking reasonable, technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information and will endeavour to continue taking all reasonable steps in order to protect your personal information and data. Wakanow will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information or data you disclose online, having regard to the nature of the internet. We may use encryption technology from time to time to assist in protecting any information or data, which you submit.
  * In any event, you accept the inherent security implications of disclosing information over the internet and agree not to hold us responsible for any breach of security unless we have been negligent or wilfully in default of our obligations under the relevant legislation.
  * At any time, if you are concerned that the information we hold about you is incorrect, or you have questions about this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us to correct such information via email or post.
  * This website contains links to other websites and Wakanow will not be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.
  * We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy and Data Protection Statement at any time by posting revisions on our Site.

**DATA SECURITY POLICY**
  * We control physical security in relation to the information and personal data that is contained at our facilities and restrict access to the site, buildings, computer rooms, office desk, technology areas, equipment and other facilities where unauthorised access by people could compromise our security.
  * All proprietary or confidential information, including personal data, is contained or stored on computer and any that is contained and stored on manual files is locked up and secure.
  * We control access to information and personal data, including existing procedures for authorising and authenticating users as well as software controls for restricting access and techniques for protecting data such as encryption.
  * We maintain a business continuity plan as a contingency plan, which identifies our business functions, and assets (including personal data) that would need to be maintained in the event of disaster and set out the procedures for protecting and restoring them if necessary.
  * In respect of detection and investigation of breaches where they occur, we have in place relevant controls, which should alert us to a breach in security. We endeavour to investigate every breach of security.
  * The Company cannot guarantee the security of any personal information or data disclosed to it or collected by it.
